



Dileep Kumar Singh Chaudhry (1) Featured

My name is Dileep Kumar Singh Chaudhry and currently i am working a job in Havells India Limited' project.

I have hold the degree of B.Tech. I have skilles of window admistration and in this company and all the employee called me Computer's Doctor.

Current Designation: Desktop Support Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Current Company: Fidelis Corporate Solutions Notice Period: 1 Month
Current Location: Delhi Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Lucknow, Jaipur, Delhi / NCR

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Tech Support Engnr

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Installation, Desktop/Tech Support Engineer, Remote Support, Configuration Management, Incident Management, System Administration, System Assembling, Outlook Configuration, Active Directory, Windows

Administration

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section | Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects

Summary

Seeking new responsibilities to explore and enhance my technical knowledge gained at my last job and current job in the last five years. I hold a B.Tech from Pratap University, Jaipur college and i had got the campus selection in 6th semester.

Work Experience

- Fidelis Corporate Solutions as Desktop Support Engineer Oct 2019 to Till Date
- 1. Create Domain account on laptop and desktop users.
- 2. Configuration and managing the group policies and user policies.
- 3. Handle the router and switch configuration.
- 4. Installation and configuration of outlook 365, 2013, 2016.
- 5. Installation and configuration of sap 7.4, 7.5.
- 6. Installation and configuration of Win-8.1, Win-10(V. 1909) and dual boot installation.
- 7. Managing encryption and decryption of Win-magic Secure-doc.
- Nating the spition and decryption of win-magic Secure-doc.
 Installation and up-gradation of operating systems from SCCM software center.
- Maintaining the incidents/ service request assigned to them till resolution.
- 10. Managing and implementation of LAN Network.
- 11. Troubleshooting LAN network and LAN connection issue.
- 12. Managing the Endpoint DLP, Symantec Antivirus, Net-scope, MCENS, One-Drive support.
- 13. Managing the online printer?s (HP Page-wide, Kyocera Task-alfa 3212i) issues.
- 14. Managing the system inventory reports
- 15. Maintaining the system via Team, SCCM remote support.
- 16. Manage the one drive data of system.
- 17. Managing the hardware and software problem.
- 18. Managing the SLA and Incident resolution.
- 19. Managing the break down time of the call.
- 20. Managing the compliance activity.21. Managing the other sites support via Teams, Zoom, SCCM remote, Any Desk, Team Viewer.
- 22. Creating the SOP?s all the software and hardware troubleshooting and installation.

Key Responsibility.

- 1. To handling the Delhi Branch with warehouses of Havells India Limited.
- 2. Ensuring client satisfaction.
- 3. Ensuring high service standards are met.
- 4. Ensuring that targeted SLAs are achieved in the said period.
- 5. Remote support to all Delhi Branch users during lockdown in Covid-19
- Kaizen It Services Private Limited as Desktop Support Engineer Jul 2015 to Oct 2019

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Project: (CBDT) Income Tax, Kanpur, Work Place - Income Tax, Kanpur, Sites ? Main office and other 5 locations in U.P.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Computers) from Pratap University, Jaipur, Rajasthan in 2015

PG: in 0

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: CCNA training

Linux administrator (RHCSA & RHCE) version 7.0 Linux administrator (RHCSA & RHCE) version 6.5,

Red Hat Open stack administrator, Computer application diploma

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience	
CCNA, Linux, LAN, SCCM		
Symantec Antivirus		
Active Directory,		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓	
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓	

^ Back to Top

Projects

Project Title: Havells India Limited

Client: Havells India Limited
Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: DELHI Role: Other

Role Description: Desktop Support Engineer

Project Details: this project of Havells India Limited, this is our client site and currently i have 8 sites in Delhi of HIL.

Project Title: CBDT

Client: Income Tax Department India Nature of Employment: Full Time

Project Location: Kanpur Role: Other

Role Description: Desktop Support Engineer

Project Details: this is project(cbdt) of related to incometax, it is related to government project, i have under the 15 sites

there.

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: SC Job Type: Permanent / Temporary
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Duration: Oct 2019 - Nov 2020

Duration: Jul 2015 - Oct 2019

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Team Size: 7

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Team Size: 1